berush.com 2017-02-21

# BeRush.com - Privacy policy

At BeRush, we strive to develop innovative services to better serve our Affiliates (as defined in BeRush Affiliate Program Terms). We recognize that privacy is an important issue, so we design and operate our services with the protection of your privacy in mind. This Privacy Policy outlines the types of information we gather when you participate in BeRush Affiliate Program, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard it. When we use the terms “BeRush”, “SEMrush”, “we”, “us” or “our”, it means Semrush Inc., a Delaware corporation, with its principal place of business at 8 Neshaminy Interplex, Suite 207, Trevose, PA 19053, USA.

## PRIVACY POLICY

Our Privacy Policy explains what information we collect and why we collect it.   
How we use that information.   
The choices we offer, including how to access and update information.   
Your privacy matters to us so whether you are new to BeRush Affiliate Program or have been our Affiliate for a long time, please take some time to get to know our practices – and if you have any questions, please do not hesitate to contact us at: MAIL@BERUSH.COM   
Our Privacy Policy (together with BeRush Affiliate Program Terms and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following Privacy Policy carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. By visiting berush.com or semrush.com (and any associated sub-domains) (“our website”), or participating in our BeRush Affiliate Program, you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this policy.

## INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We collect information to provide better services to all of our Affiliates.   
BeRush collects personal information such as your name, surname, email address, account information, billing address, company name when you register to identify you and W-8BEN/W-8BEN-E/W-9 form to transfer your commission to your account. We also collect your non-personally identifiable information such as your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your query and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. We use this information to operate, develop and improve our services.

## PARTICIPATION IN BERUSH AFFILIATE PROGRAM

We use the information we collect from all of our services to provide, maintain, protect and improve them, to develop new ones, and to protect us and our Affiliates.   
BeRush provides the service, that SEMrush has developed and operates, which allows the Affiliates to participate in BeRush Affiliate Program, where you, the Affiliate who owns or operates a website (internet domain) use marketing methods to drive traffic to semrush.com (“Service”). You also understand that the Service may include certain communications from BeRush, such as service announcements, administrative messages and that these communications are considered part of BeRush Affiliate Program. Unless explicitly stated otherwise, any new features that augment or enhance the current Service, including the release of new BeRush properties, and any related third party marketing companies, shall be subject to this Agreement. You are responsible for obtaining access to the Service, and that access may involve third-party fees (such as Internet service provider or airtime charges). Additionally, you must provide and are responsible for all equipment necessary to access the Service.

## INFORMATION WE SHARE

BeRush does not share your personal information with third parties or public except our service providers, such as SMTP infrastructure providers and payment processors, resellers, performing services on our behalf. These service providers may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use such information for any other purposes.   
Occasions when BeRush can deem it necessary to release Affiliate information including but not limited to: 

  * when requested to do so by law enforcement agencies;
  * when obliged to do so under the law of the United States of America;
  * for the purpose of pursuing outstanding debts or liabilities;
  * when given permission to do so by said Affiliate.

We do not share personal information with companies, organizations and individuals outside of BeRush unless one of the following circumstances applies:

  * we may share aggregated, non­personally identifiable information publicly and with our partners – such as publishers, advertisers or connected websites. For example, we may publicly show trends about the general use of our Services; 
  * if BeRush is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, we will continue to ensure the confidentiality of any personal information and give affected Affiliates notice before personal information is transferred or becomes subject to a different privacy policy; 
  * you can object to the use of your personal data for commercial purpose at any time.

## INFORMATION STORAGE

By submitting your personal information, you agree to its transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.   
Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access your Account, and you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share password with anyone.   
Unfortunately, the transmission of information via Internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our website; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try and prevent unauthorised access.

## INFORMATION SECURITY

We work hard to protect BeRush and our Affiliates from unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of information we hold. We review our information collection, storage and processing practices, including physical security measures, to guard against unauthorized access to systems.   
We work hard to restrict access to personal information, except for a limited number of BeRush employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it for us, and who are subject to strict contractual confidentiality obligations and may be disciplined or terminated if they fail to meet these obligations.   
To prevent being a phishing website victim, always check domain details when you are providing your personal information. Please, be aware that if you suspect the website you’re on is a fake berush.com or semrush.com website, contact us directly.

## WHEN THIS PRIVACY POLICY APPLIES

Our Privacy Policy applies to your participation in BeRush Affiliate Program.   
Our Privacy Policy does not apply to services offered by other companies or individuals. Our Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of other companies and organizations who advertise our Services, and who may use cookies, pixel tags and other technologies to serve and offer relevant ads.

## COMPLIANCE AND COOPERATION WITH REGULATORY AUTHORITIES

We regularly review our compliance with our Privacy Policy. We also adhere to several self-regulatory frameworks. When we receive formal written complaints, we will contact the person who made the complaint to follow up. We work with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that we cannot resolve with our users directly.

## CHANGES

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we may provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of privacy policy changes). The actual Privacy Policy for your review is placed on https://www.berush.com/privacy-policy.

## CONTACT

Questions, comments and requests regarding this Privacy Policy are welcome and should be addressed to us via email at mail@berush.com; or via mail to 8 NESHAMINY INTERPLEX, STE 207, TREVOSE, PA 19053, USA.
